<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crops on Harvey&#39;s Seed</title>
    <link>/crops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crops on Harvey&#39;s Seed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:27:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/crops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Alfalfa</title>
      <link>/crops/alfalfa/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/crops/alfalfa/</guid>
      <description>The only independent alfalfa breeding program in the U.S. Legacy Seeds is excited about alfalfa! Our alfalfa breeding program began in 2000 and has since introduced many excellent varieties, including L-449 APH2, L-455 HD and multiple private-label varieties that perform exceptionally well on the farm and in university yield trials. Legacy Seeds is the only company with StandLife Genetics™ protection against multiple strains of Aphanomyces Race 2 for those soils with tougher disease challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cover Crops</title>
      <link>/crops/cover-crops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/crops/cover-crops/</guid>
      <description>Harvey&amp;rsquo;s offers a variety of cover cropping and forage options to fit your operation. These include:
 Red clover Radish Pasture &amp;amp; turf mixes  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Plots</title>
      <link>/crops/food-plots/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/crops/food-plots/</guid>
      <description>Harvey&amp;rsquo;s Seed is proud to offer custom feed mixes for calf, cattle, dairy, equine, poulty, swine, and deer. Harvey&amp;rsquo;s has the ability to custom tailor feed mixes for your specific goals.
FOR A COMPLETE LIST OF FEED OFFERINGS OR TO SPEAK WITH A NUTRITIONIST, CALL (989) 584-3466</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soybeans</title>
      <link>/crops/soybeans/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/crops/soybeans/</guid>
      <description>Michigan proven, Michigan grown, exported to the world DF wants every grower to succeed, but there is no silver bullet. What works in Iowa, or Indiana, or Ohio may not work at home in Michigan. DF Seeds chooses the best traits to solve the problems on your farm, in your county, in your particular slice of the state. Harvest after harvest DF proves that you don’t need billboards and an advertising budget to grow great seed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wheat</title>
      <link>/crops/wheat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/crops/wheat/</guid>
      <description>Elite wheat from seven breeding programs DFender Seed Treatment is included on all DF wheat seed. DFender seed treatment “protects your genetic potential” by defending against seedling diseases, wireworms, and aphids. DFender uses four fungicides and an insecticide to protect wheat seedlings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>